Wimonsiri Pokasame

Frontend Developer

wpakasame@gmail.com (+66) 622238855 www.linkedin.com/in/wimonsiri75 https://pangp.herokuapp.com



Profile

Versatile Frontend Developer with 4 years of experience in blending the art of design with skill of programming to deliver an immersive and engaging user experience through efficient website development, building and maintaining responsive website, and relentless debugging.

Education

Bachelor's degree in Information Technology

May 2012 - May 2015 | King Mongkut's Institute of Technology Ladkrabang

Work Experiences

Front End Developer ---- Pronto Marketing

August 2020 - February 2021 (Contract) | Bangkok, TH

Complete website updates, involving HTML, CSS Javascript or PHP for clients. Troubleshoot website issues reported by Project Managers, Support Engineers and train support engineers to be able to write javascript and troubleshoot conflicts on websites.

Senior Front End Developer - SE Digital

February 2020 - August 2020 (Full-time) | Bangkok, TH

Developed an ICO Portal website platform with Vue.js and Nuxt which includes user authorization with AWS Cognito and token management with blockchain RTC API. Collaborated with designers, backend developers to design, build, test and improve web products.

Front End Designer — Ahancer UX/UI Agency

September 2019 - January 2020 (Contract) | Bangkok, TH

Working closely with various talented designers, developed and designed web and mobile app UI. Working on some UX Projects, preparing and presenting mockups to internal team and key stakeholders, creating wireframe and hi-fi interactive prototypes, developing website dashboard used for managing internal projects.

Front End Developer — Pronto Marketing

June 2016 - August 2019 | Bangkok, TH

Developed code to convert design mockups to websites on Wordpress. Work closely with Web Producers to complete projects accurately and on time. Provide occational assistance to web designers to ensure features in the design phase can be produced during development.

Language

Thai Native English Intermediate

Skills

HTML/CSS/SCSS/LESS/Bootstrap

Javascript/ES6/JQuery

Pug

PHP

VueJS, Nuxt

Wordpress, Woocommerce

UX/UI Design, Web Design

Tools

Docker

Postman

Trello, Jira

VS Code

Adobe Photoshop/XD/Illustrator

Github, Gitlab

Figma

Sketch

Zeplin

Invision

Webpack

Babel

AWS

Publication

Romanized Thai Input Method Editor

Year: 2017 Publisher: IEEE